IBRAHIM ONUR SERBETCI

PROFILE

Industrial Engineering major (3.04 GPA) currently attending MEF University, with 10 months of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of advanced technology, machine learning, optimization and statistics skills to successfully be a Data Scientist. Frequently praised as hardworking by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

HARD SKILLS

SOFT SKILLS

- R
- Constructing Predictive Models
- Python
- Data Analysis
- Machine Learning
- Java
- Statistical Analysis
- Data Wrangling
- SQL
- Microsoft Office

- Analytical Thinking
 - Presentation
 - Critical Thinking
 - Creativity
 - Communication
 - Collaboration

CONTACT

Mobile: +90 537-017-3333 ionurserbetci@gmail.com 123 Ince kas Street, Istanbul LinkedIn: @ionur-serbetci

REFERENCES

- References avaliable upon request.

WORK EXPERIENCE

OPERATIONS INTERN

Sanko Holding | Jun. 2019 to Jul 2019

- Support to review production schedules, engineering specifications, orders, and related information to obtain knowledge of manufacturing methods, procedures, and activities.
- Estimate production costs, cost-saving methods, and the effects of product design changes on expenditures for management review, action, and control.

ERP DEVELOPER INTERN

Acrome Robotics | Oct. 2018 to Dec. 2018

- Carrying out product classification and coding processes in production systems with a team.
- Create Amazon AWS ec2 instance for the company.
- Strengthening the Odoo ERP system used in the company by developing a new Odoo environment.

FINANCIAL AND BUSINESS ANALYSIS INTERN Volkswagen Financial Services | Aug. 2018 to Sep. 2018

- Supporting the evaluation and processing of credit for truck and bus in the VDF credit assessment department.
- Supporting the financial analysis making process for companies' credit applications.
- Systematizing the archiving of credit application contracts and help to register to the VDF.net system.
- Supporting the credit configuration process.

SUPPLY CHAIN EFFICIENCY INTERN

BSH Home Appliances Group | Jun. 2018 to Aug. 2018

- Supporting to prepare production plans for oven factory assembly lines and support international logistics and procurement processes by using SAP PP and SAP MM.
- $\hbox{-} Support for preparing reports on logistics performance measures.} \\$
- Provide ongoing analyses in areas such as transportation costs, parts procurement, backorders, or delivery processes.

EDUCATION

MEF UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Science in Industrial Engineering

- Years Attended: 2015 to 2020
- Member of IEEE
- Coursework in Probability and Statistics I-II, Introduction to Machine Learning, Operations Research I-II, Marketing Analytics, Explanatory Data Analytics, Information Systems, Modeling and Methods in Optimization, Decision Analysis and Business Intelligence
- Honor Degree in Spring 2016-2017, Spring 2017-2018, Fall 2019-2020
- GPA: 3.04